Okay,Rach,that's muffin and espresso,$4.50.
瑞秋，松饼加浓缩咖啡4块5
Ross,double latte,$2.75. Chandler,coffee and a scone,$4.25.
罗斯，双份拿铁2块7毛5 钱德，咖啡和小圆饼4块2毛5
And Phoebe,herbal tea,$1.25.
菲比，花茶，1块2毛5
All together that's $12.75.
总共是…12块7毛5
This coming from the man who couldn't split our $80 phone bill in half.
这是80元电话费除以二 不会除的人
How much do I owe you?
我的松饼和拿铁多少钱？
That's on the house, courtesy of Joey Tribbiani.
你的由乔伊崔比亚尼免费招待
Great. Well,tell him thanks.
真好，帮我谢谢他
And since Joey seems like such a nice guy...
既然乔伊人这么好
maybe we could go out?
也许我们可以约个会
He's not used to women being so forward...
他不太习惯女人这么主动
but I could check with him. He says it's okay.
不过我问过他，他说好
Great. Thanks. Bye-bye.
太好了，谢谢，再见
How come our stuff isn't free?
乔伊，为什么我们不是免费？
It will be when you look like that in a tight skirt.
等你穿窄裙也那么辣就可以免费了
I'm getting more dates than ever.
真好，我的约会破记录的多
You're only giving free stuff to the pretty girls?
慢着，你只算美女免费？
Joey,that is so gross!
对啊，好恶心喔
How about a scone on the house,baby?
要不要来一块免费小圆饼？
I'm pretty.
我是美女
The One With Rachel's Sister
本集播出：“姐妹大比拼”
rainystar压制iPod-MP4
-Hey,does anyone have any gum? -I do.
有人有口香糖吗？ 我有
Here. Sorry.
拿一下
Oh,you know what?
好像是…
No.
不是
Wait a second.
等一下
-I know it's in here. -You know what? I'm good.
我记得我有 算了，不用了
Sorry,I guess it's in my big bag.
抱歉，大概在我的大袋子里
Say,does anybody have a goldfish?
有人有金鱼吗？
Why are you here? Shouldn't you be at work?
你怎么回来了？不是在上班？
They sent me home. They said I can't work if I'm sick.
他们叫我回家 说什么感冒不能做菜
-Sorry you're sick. -I'm not sick!
-真可怜 -我没有感冒
I don't get sick. Getting sick is for weaklings, it's for pansies.
我才不会感冒 软弱和娘娘腔的人才会感冒
No one thinks that you're a pansy...
没有人觉得你娘娘腔
but we do think that you need a tissue.
但我们觉得你需要面纸
I have not been sick in over three years.
我已经3年多没感冒了
I think you're sick because that used to be in your nose.
我觉得你感冒了，因为…… 那个原本在你的鼻子里
I'll get tissue.
我帮你拿几张面纸
I don't need a tissue. I'm fine-d.
我不需要面纸，我很好…哪
When you put a D at the end of fine...
好的后面还加个哪
you're not fine.
就是不好哪
I'm fine-d.
我很好…哪
It's a really hard word to say.
这句话很难说
-Yes? -Hi. Is Rachel here? I'm her sister.
-哪一位？ -瑞秋在吗？我是她的妹妹
Oh,my God,Jill!
天哪，吉儿
Oh,my God,Rachel!
天哪，瑞秋
Oh,my God,introduce us.
天哪，介绍一下吧
This is Chandler. And you know Monica and Ross.
这位是钱德 你认识摩妮卡和罗斯
And that's Phoebe. And that's Joey.
那是菲比，那是乔伊
-How you doing? -Don't!
-你好吗？ -别……
Honey,what are you doing here?
你怎么来了？
Which sister is this?
这是哪个妹妹？
Is this the spoiled one or the one that bit her?
被宠坏的还是愤世嫉俗的？
Daddy cut me off.
老爸断了我的财源
Never mind,I got it.
我知道了
You know what I said?
你知道我怎么说？
I said,"I'll hire a lawyer, sue you,take all your money...
我说 “我要请一个律师 把你的钱都告过来”
and cut you off!"
“然后断了你的财源”
Wow. What did he say?
那他怎么说？
That he wouldn't pay for my lawyer.
他说不帮我付律师费
Then he told me to learn the value of money...
还叫我跟他唯一自豪的女儿
from the one daughter he's actually proud of.
来学学金钱的价值
Did you hear that? My dad's proud of me.
你们听到了吗？我爸以我为荣
My dad's proud of me.
我爸以我为荣
-Rach? -Oh,yeah. Sorry.
-瑞秋？ -好，抱歉
Honey,so what did you do that made Dad cut you off?
爸为什么不给你钱？
Okay,I bought a boat.
我买了一艘船
You bought a boat?
你买了一艘船？
It wasn't for me, it was for a friend.
不是我要的，是要送朋友的
Boy,did we make friends with the wrong sister.
我们不该跟姐姐交朋友的
I knew it was stupid and I shouldn't have done it...
我知道这样很蠢很不应该
but she bought me all these CDs and said I had a cute haircut.
但她送我一大堆CD 还说我的发型很漂亮
And your daddy didn't understand?
而你爸却不能理解？
I know,and usually I just cry and say I'm sorry and he forgives me.
就是啊 通常我哭着道歉就没事了
Oh,yes,good criers,the Green girls.
没错，格林家的女生最会哭了
I mean,the Green sisters.
我是说格林家的姐妹
Man,no matter how you say it...
不管怎么说...
it still sounds like you're talking about green people.
听起来都像蛤蜊
I'm at rock bottom.
我真是冷到极点
This is the best thing that could've happened to you.
吉儿，这是一次最好的教训
You've needed to get out on your own.
反正你也得独立
When I did it, at first I was scared, but then look at me now.
我刚独立时也很害怕 结果现在呢
I am the only daughter that Dad is proud of.
我是唯一让老爸骄傲的女儿
I can't believe him. How does he expect me to buy stuff?
他真是太扯了 我要怎么买东西？
Maybe,you know, you won't buy stuff for a while.
那你就先不要买东西
I don't understand.
我不懂
This is what you'll do. You're gonna get a job.
你现在要做的是找一份工作
You're gonna get an apartment.
找一间公寓
And then you will live off the money that you earn.
然后靠你自己赚的钱过活
Okay,I know this is what you did...
好，我知道你是这样
but that doesn't sound like me.
但这不像我的作风
Okay,but it can be. It can be you.
但你可以做得到 我会帮你
And you can stay with us. Right,Phoebe?
你可以跟我们住 菲比，可以吧？
-Of course, yeah. -Oh,that's so great!
-当然可以 -太好了
Okay,I'm really gonna do this. I don't know how to thank you.
好，那我就来独立 真不知道该怎么谢谢你们
Oh,I like cars.
我喜欢汽车
-You all finished? -Yes.
-你吃完了吗？ -吃完了
Great.
太好了
Okay,here are the tips for this morning.
早上的小费出来了
Jen gets 50, 50 for me and Joey owes 8 dollars.
珍50，我50 乔伊欠8块钱
-What? -For all the free food you gave away.
-什么？ -因为你到处送吃的
If it's free, how come you're charging me for it?
既然是送的，为什么跟我要钱
We don't give anything away unless it's a birthday.
我们只免费招待寿星
What if they came in third in a modeling contest?
那模特儿比赛第三名呢？
No.
不行
Sorry.
抱歉
I just had the hardest day. Some of these are so heavy.
我今天好惨，这些袋子好重
How did you pay? I thought your dad took your credit card.
吉儿，你怎么有钱？ 你爸不是把信用卡都收走了？
I memorized those numbers when I was 15.
拜托，我15岁就会背卡号了
But look at all the cool make-it-on-my-own stuff I got!
你们看我买的这些独立行头
This is my "Please hire me" sweater.
这是“请雇佣我”毛衣p
And these are my "Don't you want to rent me this apartment?" pants.
这是 “你不想把房子租我吗”裤子
Charging clothes to your dad doesn't qualify as making it on your own.
让你爸付你的置装费不算独立
Oh, Mr. Scientist has to get all technical.
大科学家就是这么死板
Rachel's not gonna think it's a good idea.
瑞秋真的不会赞成
-So who made her queen of the world? -I would love that job!
-谁封她当女王了？ -我超想当女王的
What's going on?
怎么样啊？
Jill!
吉儿
Did you shop?
你跑去逛街吗？
No.
没有
They did.
是他们
Yeah,we went shopping!
对，我们跑去逛街
You went shopping?
你们跑去逛街？
Then you came here and paraded it under Jill's nose...
然后把东西秀给吉儿看？
when you know she's trying to quit. That's terrible.
你们明知她想戒掉 你们真差劲
Sorry,Jill.
抱歉 吉儿
So,what'd you get?
你们买了什么？
Oh,well,all right. Thank you.
我买了…谢谢p
I got this, you know, "I want a job" sweater.
我买了这件 “我要工作”毛衣
And then I got.. These are apartment pants.
还买了这条公寓裤
Apartment pants?
公寓裤？
You've never heard of them?
对，你没听过吗？
Of course I've heard of them.
当然听过
Ross,what'd you get?
罗斯那你呢？
I got this...
我买了这个…
This.
这个
-A pashmina? -Yeah!
帕什米纳（披肩）？ 对
I love these babies.
我爱死它了
Really?
是吗？
What's a pashmina?
帕什米纳是什么？
It's a rug.
一种小毯子
Jill?
吉儿？
I'm sorry,Rachel.
瑞秋，对不起…
You think that's gonna work on me? I invented that.
拜托，你真以为我会上当？ 泪眼攻势是我发明的
Right! But I am sorry.
也对，但我真的很抱歉
It's okay. One little setback is okay.
算了，走一次回头路还好
-But don't let it happen again,okay? -Okay.
-就是别再犯了，好吗？ -好。
Now,since Daddy paid for all this stuff, I should take it all away.
既然这是老爸付的钱 我应该全都没收
But I'm just gonna take the pashmina.
不过我没收披肩就好
And the pants.
还有那条裤子
I'll take it all, because that way, you'll learn the lesson.
还是都没收好了 这样你才能得到教训
All right.
I'm gonna run a couple of errands and I will see you at dinner.
我有事要忙，我们晚餐见
She took all my stuff.
都被她拿走了
Yeah. Everything but the little blue one.
没错，除了这个蓝色小袋子
That's the best one!
这一样最棒了
Oh,my God. Thank you so much!
天哪，谢谢你
Well,hey.
Oh,my gosh,that was so lame. Like a pashmina could be a rug.
天哪，你好逊喔 帕什米纳怎么会是小毯子
Oh,yeah? How about you with the "I'm sorry"?
那你呢？“对不起…”
Shut up! I wasn't like that at all.
闭嘴，我哪有那么恶心
What about what I said about the apartment pants? How dumb was l?
我那个公寓裤呢？够蠢吧？
-Were you this cute in high school? -Oh,stop.
-你高中时有这么可爱吗？ -别闹了
-No,you stop. -No,you stop.
-你才别闹了 -你才别闹了
Why don't I sit here and then you'll both stop it?
你别闹了 好，我坐中问，你们都别闹了
Okay. So,what do you want to do?
你想做什么？
Let's do something crazy.
我们来疯一下
I know, let's rest and drink lots of fluids.
我知道，我们来多休息多喝水
Okay,I'll rest.
好，我休息
But if I'm going to bed, then you're coming with me.
不过如果我要上床 你也得跟我来
See,that would be impossible to resist if you weren't all...
我本来很难说不 但是你...
drippy here.
鼻水流不停
Are you saying that you don't want to get with this?
你是说你不想要我吗？
I don't think you should say that even when you're healthy.
你最好连健康时都不要这样
Come on.
来嘛
Don't take this personally.
我不是针对你
I just can't have sex with a sick person.
我就是没办法跟病人上床
I'm with you. I can't have sex with a sick person either. Disgusting!
我也是，我也不跟病人上床 那样好恶心
But I'm not sick!
但是我没病
Let me prove it to you.
让我证明给你看
We are two healthy people in the prime of lime.
我们身强体壮，青春正盛
See, that's the thing, I would like to stay in the "prime of lime."
我就是想继续身强体壮
Oh,okay,now I'll do it.
好，我有“性”致了
Hey. What's up?
怎么样啊？
I think there's something you should know.
有件事或许你应该知道
Better not be about the apartment pants.
最好不是公寓裤的事
I just pitched the idea to my boss at Ralph Lauren and she loved it.
因为我的上司爱死这个构想了
No. It's just,I was...
不是，我...
I was with Ross and Jill after you left...
我刚和罗斯，吉儿在一起
and I'm pretty sure I saw a little spark between them.
我很确定他们之间有火花
-What? -I mean,it's probably nothing.
什么？ 或许没事
But I wanted to warn you that there might be something.
我只是想提醒你 他们或许有什么
-With Ross and Jill? -Yeah.
-罗斯跟吉儿？ -对
With Ross and my sister?
罗斯和我妹妹？
With my sister Jill and my ex-boyfriend Ross?
我妹妹吉儿和我的前男友罗斯？
-Oh,there is no way. -Okay,then.
-不可能的 -那好吧
Oh,my God! I cannot believe that!
我的天哪，我真不敢相信
I don't like it when he dates anyone, but my sister?
不是我反对罗斯交女朋友 但跟我妹？
Isn't that incest or something?
不是等于乱伦吗？
And they're gonna have sex.
天哪，而且他们会上床
Oh,no! What if he marries her too?
要是他还娶她呢？
This is just terrible. This is just terrible.
太恐怖了，真是太恐怖了
And I can't stop it. I don't own Ross.
而我又不能阻止 罗斯又不是我的
And Jill should be able to do what she wants to do.
而且吉儿有她的行动自由
Oh, my God, I can't believe Ross is marrying my little sister.
我的天哪，罗斯居然要娶我妹妹
This is the worst thing that could've ever happened to me.
这真是我这一生最悲惨的遭遇
But great news about the apartment pants,huh?
不过公寓裤的事真是太好了
That'll be $3.85.
总共3块8毛5
What? Yesterday you said I was too pretty to pay.
什么意思？ 昨天你还说我太美不该付钱
It's just, I can't, because my manager said that I..
我不能请客，因为经理说我…
Happy birthday to you
祝你生日快乐…
-Happy birthday,dear Annie.. -Amy!
祝安妮生日快乐 艾美
Amy
艾美
Happy birthday to you
祝你生日快乐
That's weird, today's my birthday too.
真巧，今天也是我的生日
Not in here,it isn't.
在这里不是
Sorry I'm late. What's up?
抱歉迟到了，什么事？
I just wanted to see if there were any leads on the old job front.
我只是想问你工作找得怎样
No. But I walked past three sales and didn't go in.
没进展 但我经过三家折扣店都没进去
How strong am I?
我很坚强吧？
That is great.
太好了
You know who doesn't have to job-hunt? Ross.
你知道谁不必找工作？ 罗斯.
-He works at the university. -Yeah?
他在大学教书 是啊
So you guys talked? So you get along? So you're gonna go out?
所以你知道，你们聊过 你们很投缘，你们要约会吗？
Me go out with Ross? No.
我跟罗斯约会？
God,no. What would make you think that?
当然不会，你哪来的念头？
Phoebe...
这个…菲比....
said she thought she saw something between you guys.
觉得你们有什么
I mean,he's nice.
没有，他人是很好
He's the kind you're friends with, but not the kind you date.
你会想和他做朋友 但不会想和他交往
He's the kind you date, because you did. But me?
你会，你跟他交往过
Not so much.
我就没什么兴趣
Oh,not so much. What do you mean? Is there something wrong with Ross?
没什么兴趣？什么意思？ 罗斯有哪里不好吗？
No,no,no. He's just...
没有，只不过他...
I don't know. You know,he's just a little bookish.
他有点书呆
Are you saying he's a geek?
你觉得他是怪胎？
You think so too?
你也有同感？
No. Ross is not a geek.
不，罗斯不是怪胎
Then let's just say he's not my type.
好，就当他不是我喜欢的类型
Handsome is not your type?
你不喜欢帅哥？
Smart,kind,good kisser.
聪明？好心？吻技一流？
What,those things aren't on your list?
这些不是你的条件？
Ross is great. You'd be lucky to be with him.
罗斯人很好 能跟他在一起是你的福气
If it means that much, then I'll ask him out.
好，既然你这么在意 我就约他
Oh,no. That's not what I meant.
不不不，我不是那个意思
You know what? You're right.
你知道吗？你说得对
He has been really nice to me.
他对我确实很好
Yeah, but he's not your type.
但他不是你的类型
But maybe that's good.
或许这是好事
I'm doing all these different things.
我正在做各种尝试
Maybe I should just try dating a geek too.
或许也应该跟怪胎约会看看
Yeah,but you don't want to try too much too fast.
但你也别一下子做太多尝试
You remember what happened to the little girl who...
你记得那个
tried too much too fast,don't you?
一下子做太多尝试的小女孩吧
What?
什么？
She died,Jill.
她死了
Chandler!
钱德
What is it,honey? You need some tea? Some soup?
什么事，你想喝茶？ 还是喝汤？
Calling Dr. Big.
呼叫大雕医生
Dr. Big to the bed.
大雕医生请上床
Jeez,honey, I thought you were asleep.
天哪，我以为你睡了
How could I be asleep knowing that you were in the next room?
你就在外面，我怎么睡得着？
I was asleep.
我倒是睡着了
No,honey. You know what's sexy? Layers.
不，你知道怎样才性感？ 多穿几层
Layers are sexy.
多穿几层才性感
And blankets are sexy. And hot-water bottles are sexy.
被子才性感 热水瓶更性感
Get into bed. I want to prove I'm not sick.
上床啦，我想证明我没生病
I want to make you feel as good as I feel.
我想让你跟我一样舒服
Would you please get some rest?
我拜托你休息
I'm fine.
我没事哪
-You're coughing. -No,I'm not.
-你在咳嗽  -我没有
No,I'm not,I'm laughing.
我没有，我是在笑
-At what? -Just something I heard before.
-笑什么？ -我之前听说的一件事
-Tell me. -No,I don't want it to spoil the mood.
-告诉我 -不，我不想破坏情调
Happy birthday to you
祝你生日快乐
-You're paying for that. -No,it's her birthday.
你出钱 不，今天是她的生日
You've sung "Happy Birthday" to 20 women today.
你已经对二十个女人唱生日快乐
You are no longer authorized to distribute birthday muffins.
-但是… -你失去送生日松饼的权限了
Damn it!
妈的
瑞秋
Did you tell your sister to ask me out?
你叫你妹约我吗？
-Well,yeah. -Oh,wow! I mean,wow.
-对… -哇，真是……哇
I think she's cute,but...
我觉得她很可爱 但...
I never would've thought of going out with her. Never!
我从来没想过要跟她约会
Really?
真的？
But after you said it's okay, I figured,"Why not?"
不过既然然你说行 我心想：有何不可？
Oh,so not really "never."
所以也不算从来没想过
I have to say you are a much bigger person than I am.
你真的比我大方多了
I mean,after all we've been through.
我们有那么多过去
I wish I had a brother to reciprocate.
我… 真希望我有兄弟可以做交换
If you ever date Monica, you have my blessing.
如果你想跟摩妮卡交往 我绝对祝福
And mine.
我也是
Chandler?
钱德
I think I'm sick.
我觉得我病了
Really?
是吗？
Struck down in the "pribe of libe."
青春不盛了？
Okay,fine,I admit it. I feel terrible.
好啦，我承认，我很不舒服
Will you please rub this on my chest?
帮我在胸口抹药膏
No,no,no. You are not getting me this way.
不行，你别想骗我上钩
Come on,I really need your help here.
-我真的需要你帮我… -不行
-Fine,I'll rub it on myself. -Okay.
-好，那我就自己抹 -好
So you're just kind of rubbing it on yourself?
你在往身上抹药膏？
-Yeah. -It's nice.
-怎样？ -蛮好的
You kidding me? Is this turning you on?
不会吧？这样你会兴奋？
Yes.
-对
Is it the rubbing or the smell?
-真是太扯了 -是抹的动作还是味道？
It's all very,very good.
都很棒
So you want to go...
想不想…
mix it up?
嘿咻一下？
-Not now,I'm sick. -Oh,come on,you big faker!
-现在不行，我病了 -少来了，大骗子
What about never sleeping with sick people?
你不是不跟病人上床？
Well,that was before all the vaporizing action.
那是在那令人酥麻的动作之前
Okay,if you really want to have sex.
-好吧，如果你真的想做… -好
Worked like a charm.
真够灵的
Why are you here?
你来这里干什么？
This is where Ross and I are meeting for our date. So,what do you think?
我跟罗斯约在这里 我的打扮如何？
I don't like it.
我不喜欢
-Really? -It's kind of slutty.
-是吗？ -有点放荡
It's yours.
这是你的衣服
Yeah,well,I'm a slut.
我是个贱人
Me too.
我也是
Hi,Jill.
吉儿
Hi...
Rachel.
瑞秋
You're not at home, you're right here.
你不在家，你在这里
Yeah,I know.
我知道
And I bet you thought it would be weird. But it's not.
你一定以为会很怪，其实不会
Okay.
好
So,well,I'll...
我...
I'll have her home by midnight.
我午夜之前会送她回家
Why aren't you home yet?
你为什么还没回家
Is someone there?
外面有人吗？
Oh,yeah,it's me. Sorry.
有，是我，抱歉
What are you doing here?
你来干什么？
I'm just looking out your window...
我只是在看窗外…
at the view.
的风景
What are you guys doing?
你们在干什么？
We got some vapor rub in some places.
我们身上沾到药膏
He brought her back to his apartment.
他把她带回家了
Who?
谁？
Is that your sister?
那是你妹妹吗？
She is a slut!
她真是个贱人
Ross is on a date with your sister. How weird is that?
罗斯在跟你妹约会，多奇怪啊
Oh,my God, he's taking off her clothes!
天哪，看，他在脱她的衣服
He's taking off her coat.
他在帮她脱外套
Oh,this is just terrible.
真是太糟糕了
Oh,no,it's not. It's a first date. I'm sure that nothing is gonna...
不会啦，才第一次约会 一定不会有…
He's gonna get some.
他有福了…
Of the glare...
能看到...
from the streetlight out of his apartment.
屋外街灯的灯光
You know, so he's closed the drapes there...
所以他把窗帘拉上
so he can have a nice,pleasant...
好跟你妹妹...
conversation with your little sister.
好好聊一聊
Well,I'm off to bed.
我去睡了
（未完待续）
I don't feel good.
我不舒服
You better not get me sick.
别把感冒传染给我
I need some fruit or some juice or some....
我需要水果或果汁或…
Or some nothing.
或空气
There's nothing in here. Who took our food?
冰箱是空的 谁拿了我们的食物？
Can I interest you in a slice of lasagna or a drumstick?
要不要来点千层面或鸡腿？
-No,thanks. -Are you sure? It's on the house.
不用了 你确定？免费的喔
-No,thanks. -How about going out with me Friday night?
-不用了 -星期五晚上要不要跟我约会？
-No,thanks. -What are you gonna do.
-不了 -那就没办法了